University Photography Photograph Collection UA206
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 2005 -- 2006; UA206.001; 3347 Digital Object(s)
  - Job 050826 BLO Tree Topping, 2005; UA206.001.187; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 063, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00013; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 043, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00014; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 013, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00015; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 109, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00016; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 078, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00017; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 023, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00018; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 084, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00019; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 021, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00020; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 097, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00021; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 068, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00022; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 019, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00023; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 108, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00024; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 093, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00025; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 077, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00026; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 060, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00027; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 049, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00028; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 048, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00029; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 045, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00030; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 037, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00031; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 034, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00032; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 022, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00033; Loeb, Brian
    - The last major beam is lifted onto Sophia Gordon Hall after being signed by construction workers. Photo 009, 2005-08-26; UA206.001.187.00034; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050827 BLO Sailing, 2005; UA206.001.188; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050828 ASC Sailing, 2005; UA206.001.189; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050829 BLO construction, 2005; UA206.001.190; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050830 ASC Dental Tour, 2005; UA206.001.191; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050830 BLO Dental Tour, 2005; UA206.001.192; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 137, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Dental Family Welcome. A tour of the facilities of the School of Dental Medicine, given to the parents and families of newly-enrolled students.
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 103, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 069, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 036, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 120, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 067, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00006; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 048, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00007; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 026, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00008; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 148, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00009; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 095, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00010; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 033, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00011; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 012, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00012; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 145, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00013; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 003, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00014; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 108, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00015; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 132, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00016; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 142, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00017; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 091, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00018; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 077, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00019; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 053, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00020; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 162, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00021; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 116, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00022; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 082, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00023; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 005, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00024; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 126, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00025; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 092, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00026; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 064, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00027; Loeb, Brian
    - Dental Family Welcome. Photo 020, 2005-08-30; UA206.001.192.00028; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050830 BLO McClennan, 2005; UA206.001.193; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050830 MKO Innocenzo Hate, 2005; UA206.001.194; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050830 MKO Pollacia, 2005; UA206.001.195; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050831 ASC Advising, 2005; UA206.001.196; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 007, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00001; Schutzengel, Aaron
      Matriculation 2005. Students meet with their peer advisors in classrooms in the Olin Center.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 052, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00002; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 032, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00003; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 002, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00004; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 057, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00005; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 040, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00006; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 014, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00007; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 012, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00008; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 011, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.196.00009; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050831 ASC Balloons, 2005; UA206.001.197; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050831 ASC Lunch, 2005; UA206.001.198; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 004, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.198.00001; Schutzengel, Aaron
      Matriculation 2005. Students and their parents eat lunch on the President's Lawn before the matriculation ceremony.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 007, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.198.00002; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 006, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.198.00003; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 015, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.198.00004; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 016, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.198.00005; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050831 ASC Matriculation, 2005; UA206.001.199; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 200, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00001; Schutzengel, Aaron
      Matriculation 2005. Matriculation Ceremony on the academic quad.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 198, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00002; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 188, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00003; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 180, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00004; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 178, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00005; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 137, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00006; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 124, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00007; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 116, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00008; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 084, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00009; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 046, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00010; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 043, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00011; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 006, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00012; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 098, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00013; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 019, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00014; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 065, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00015; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 228, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00016; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 216, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00017; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 108, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00018; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 094, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00019; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 189, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00020; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 064, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00021; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 207, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00022; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 118, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00023; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 101, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00024; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 038, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00025; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 231, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00026; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 221, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00027; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 165, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00028; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 142, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00029; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 121, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00030; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 168, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00031; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 156, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00032; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 073, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00033; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 219, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00034; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 205, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00035; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 127, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00036; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 122, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00037; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 113, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00038; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 109, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00039; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 096, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00040; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 012, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00041; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 011, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00042; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 001, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00043; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 230, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00044; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 141, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00045; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 031, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00046; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 191, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00047; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 174, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00048; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 157, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00049; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 075, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00050; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 048, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00051; Schutzengel, Aaron
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 222, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.199.00052; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050831 ASC Moving, 2005; UA206.001.200; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050831 ASC students, 2005; UA206.001.201; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050831 BLO Advising, 2005; UA206.001.202; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050831 BLO Balloons, 2005; UA206.001.203; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 008, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Matriculation 2005. Orientation volunteers blowing up balloons in Dowling Hall 701 and distribute them around campus before the new class arrives. Includes Orientation Coordinators Anita Sinha, LA '06, and Kate Drizos, LA '06.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 005, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 013, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 003, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 006, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 015, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00006; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 012, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00007; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 011, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00008; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 004, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00009; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 002, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.203.00010; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050831 BLO Lunch, 2005; UA206.001.204; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 011, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00001; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 013, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 002, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 007, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 016, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 015, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00006; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 005, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00007; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 008, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.204.00008; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050831 BLO Matriculation, 2005; UA206.001.205; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050831 BLO Moving, 2005; UA206.001.206; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 057, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Matriculation 2005. Students moving in to their rooms in Wren Hall, Hill Hall and Metcalf Hall. Includes Orientation Coordinator Kate Drizos, LA '06.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 036, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 024, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 021, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 012, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 018, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00006; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 005, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00007; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 055, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00008; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 047, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00009; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 028, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00010; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 020, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00011; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 007, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00012; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 050, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00013; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 001, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00014; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 033, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00015; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 022, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00016; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 052, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00017; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 040, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00018; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 032, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00019; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 027, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00020; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 023, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00021; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 019, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00022; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 015, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00023; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 006, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00024; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 039, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00025; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 026, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00026; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 014, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.206.00027; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050831 BLO Sports, 2005; UA206.001.207; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 001, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.207.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Matriculation 2005. Students and parents attend fall sports meetings with coaches. Sailing, men's soccer, football, and field hockey.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 005, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.207.00002; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050831 BLO Welcome Ceremony, 2005; UA206.001.208; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 148, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Matriculation 2005. The Welcome Ceremony in the Gantcher Family Sports and Convocation Center.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 139, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 119, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 063, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 060, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 031, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00006; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 137, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00007; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 144, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00008; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 113, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00009; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 085, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00010; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 058, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00011; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 013, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00012; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 074, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00013; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 042, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00014; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 128, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00015; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 105, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00016; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 061, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00017; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 040, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00018; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 065, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00019; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 054, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00020; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 001, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00021; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 126, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00022; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 110, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00023; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 134, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00024; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 008, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00025; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 104, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00026; Loeb, Brian
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 057, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.208.00027; Loeb, Brian
  - Job 050831 JHI TUSM, 2005; UA206.001.209; Hilton, Jodi
  - Job 050831 JTO Moving, 2005; UA206.001.210; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 182, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00001; Tobin, Joanie
      Matriculation 2005. Students moving in to their rooms. Includes roommates Niove Theoharides and Brittany Holiday.
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 177, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00002; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 169, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00003; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 127, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00004; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 113, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00005; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 039, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00006; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 033, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00007; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 028, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00008; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 016, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00009; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 199, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00010; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 148, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00011; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 093, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00012; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 212, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00013; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 207, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00014; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 183, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00015; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 171, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00016; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 119, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00017; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 047, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00018; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 040, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00019; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 029, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00020; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 022, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00021; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 017, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00022; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 012, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00023; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 206, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00024; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 153, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00025; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 100, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00026; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 075, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00027; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 194, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00028; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 174, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00029; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 121, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00030; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 036, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00031; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 027, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00032; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 120, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00033; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 109, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00034; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 038, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00035; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 026, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00036; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 015, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00037; Tobin, Joanie
    - Matriculation 2005. Photo 163, 2005-08-31; UA206.001.210.00038; Tobin, Joanie